evilbeetgossip.com 2017-06-24

# Privacy Policy - Today's Evil Beet Gossip – Today's Celebrity Gossip from Evil Beet Gossip

**Evil Beet Gossip AACG, LLC Privacy Policy**  
_This document was last updated December 31, 2010._

This Privacy Policy covers Evil Beet Gossip AACG, LLC and its majority-owned affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively, “EvilBeet” or “EBG”). EvilBeet is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how EvilBeet collects and utilizes your personal information when you use our services.

**WHY DO WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
EvilBeet collects personal information to improve the manner by which we operate and offer our services, communicate with you about those services, and provide effective, timely support when needed. We will never rent or sell any of the personally-identifiable information we collect from you to third parties, and will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties without your consent, unless such sharing is necessary for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**  
You must register or post a comment on the EvilBeet web site(s) before any personally identifiable information is available to EvilBeet. Information gathered during these processes may differ based on the nature of the action. Information that you provide when registering or commenting, may include: name and email address; contact information; information concerning the post on which you have commented; content accessed or downloaded through EBG services; location information (such as zip code or postal code and country); computer configuration (such as operating system, connection speed, and peripherals); the IP Internet (IP) address and URL of the Website that sent you to the EvilBeet web site; and demographic information provided by you (such as language, gender and age, and, if applicable, content preferences and personalization information). As of the date of this privacy policy, EvilBeet does not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

We will not sell, rent or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent, except as set forth below.

**HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE?**  
EvilBeet understands that it is a privilege to have you as a customer and is committed to protecting your personal information. We use the following controls to protect your personal information:

– Use of security controls to restrict access to databases housing personally identifying information;  
– Use of up to date, continually monitored software platforms to minimize or eliminate common security exposures;  
– Restrict employee access to databases containing personal information and impose confidentiality requirements upon employees who do; and  
– Bind subcontractors with contractual, technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information.

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
EvilBeet uses your personal information to:

– Deliver to you EvilBeet services, and communicate with you concerning your services and customer support issues.  
– Improve our services by providing personalized content recommendations, language and location customization, and/or personalized content delivery based on your preferences;  
– Track content accesses to ensure relevant content is continually provided through the EvilBeet services;  
– Provide you with content, services, and a more personalized experience based on personal information, such as your language preferences, zip/postal code, country locations, and any content or other preferences you provide;  
– Provide you with news, free newsletters, updates, targeted advertising, promotions, and special offers; and  
– Better understand how our products are used, including Web traffic patterns and what types of content are most popular with users of our products and services.

**WHEN AND HOW DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES?**  
EvilBeet does not use your personal information for purposes incompatible with those listed above. EvilBeet does not sell, rent, or share your personal information to a third party unless you consent to provide such information to a third party partner or content service.

In some cases, access to certain services, such as products distributed by third parties, may require the provision of personal information to a third party, such as a content provider or distributor. In such cases, this will be stated during the registration process, in the terms of use, through the distribution process, or in a similar manner. The third party’s use of such information is governed by that party’s privacy policy, and EvilBeet’s use is governed by this privacy policy. Please visit the privacy policy of the content partner to make sure you understand how they use the personal information you provide to them. If you do not wish for such a transfer to take place, you should not register for the applicable product or service. Additionally, EvilBeet may be required to provide specific access and usage information to certain content providers and other stakeholders as a condition of content licensing. In such cases, EvilBeet may provide content usage, access, demographic and other information without your personally identifiable information (your name, contact information, email address) to the content provider.

EvilBeet may disclose relevant information about our customers to our contractors (e.g. a customer service contractor) in order for them to provide specific services for EvilBeet, and to better serve our customers. EvilBeet’s contractors are bound by strict contractual requirements to keep all personal information they process strictly confidential and to use such information solely on behalf of EvilBeet.

Also, EvilBeet may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law; (b) comply with the order of a competent judicial authority in any jurisdiction; (c) comply with legal process served on EvilBeet; (d) protect and defend the rights or property of EvilBeet; or (e) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of EvilBeet products or the public at large.

EvilBeet websites, products and services contain links to other websites, and products and services. For example, EvilBeet may offer a promotion with a content partner. Because EvilBeet does not manage such promotions, products and services, they are NOT governed by this privacy policy. EvilBeet is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites or products. Please visit the privacy policies of these third party sites in order to understand their privacy policies and data collection practices.

**E-MAIL FROM EVILBEET**  
Registering with EvilBeet, where available, allows you to tell us how or whether you want EvilBeet to communicate with you. Generally, we send e-mail to you about our content and special offers. Separate EvilBeet services may send separate newsletters and marketing emails. During registration, you may opt out of receiving EvilBeet marketing e-mails and/or newsletters for the relevant product or service.

**HOW TO ACCESS AND UPDATE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
To update your personal information, please contact support via the EvilBeet contact page on the web site at <http://www.evilbeetgossip.com/contact/> with your request.

**SECURITY OF PERSONAL AND PAYMENT INFORMATION**

**Use of Cookies  
**Like other major Websites, we use cookies to provide you with a tailored experience when visiting our Websites. We also use cookies to understand traffic patterns on EvilBeet Websites and to authorize access to certain features. We treat any personal information that may be contained in cookies with the same level of confidentiality as other information you provide to us.

EvilBeet does not require that you accept cookies, however, some functionality on our Websites may be disabled if you decline to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**  
We frequently revise this Privacy Policy to keep it up to date with EvilBeet services and Web pages. “Updated” may be used to alert users to recent changes and to the date of the last update.

**NON-US CUSTOMER INFORMATION**  
If you are a customer who is logging on from outside the United States, the personal information you submit to EvilBeet will be sent to and stored in servers in our U.S. datacenters. The personal information practices set out in this Privacy Policy apply to all EvilBeet’s customers worldwide.

**NO ERROR FREE PERFORMANCE**  
We customarily release new features of our services which are early stage releases and are further refined before the release of the final version. Because these products are still in a test phase, we may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. As such, we welcome feedback on any privacy concerns you may have, and on how to improve our products generally, in all stages of release. EvilBeet does not guarantee error-free performance under this privacy policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this privacy policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our privacy policy. EvilBeet shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the United States.

**CONTACT US ABOUT PRIVACY**  
If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our products or services or would like to make a complaint, please contact us via mail or the web site at:

Privacy Concerns  
Evil Beet Gossip AACG, LLC  
P.O. Box 1295  
Westminster, MD 21158  
<http://www.evilbeetgossip.com/contact/>
